<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kevin D. Stubbs&#39;s homepage on Kevin D. Stubbs</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kevin D. Stubbs&#39;s homepage on Kevin D. Stubbs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 10:15:35 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>wannier-functions-notes</title>
      <link>/notes/wannier_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 10:15:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/notes/wannier_notes/</guid>
      <description>Notes on Wannier Functions  Outline  A Quick Introduction to Bloch Functions  Notational Setup Periodic Hamiltonians and Bloch Functions The Problem of Finding Wannier Functions   Wannier Functions and Parallel Transport Gauge  Construction of Wannier Functions The Gauge Freedom Parallel Transport Gauge (IN PROGRESS)   The Haldane Model (IN PROGRESS)    A Quick Introduction to Bloch Functions Notational Setup  \(\Lambda\) is the lattice spanned with Bravais lattice vectors \(\bm{v}_1, \bm{v}_2\): \[\Lambda = \{ n_1 \bm{v}_1 + n_2 \bm{v}_2 : n_1, n_2 \in \Z^2 \}\] \(\Lambda^*\) is the dual lattice to \(\Lambda\) spanned by \(\bm{w}_1, \bm{w}_2\) satisfying \(\bm{v}_i \cdot \bm{w}_j = 2 \pi \delta_{ij}\) \[ \Lambda^* = \{ n_1 \bm{w}_1 + n_2 \bm{w}_2 : n_1, n_2 \in \Z^2 \} \] \(\Omega = \R^2 / \Lambda\) is a fundamental cell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers - Kevin D. Stubbs&#39;s homepage</title>
      <link>/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/papers/</guid>
      <description>Jianfeng Lu and Kevin D Stubbs. Algebraic localization of Wannier functions implies Chern triviality in non-periodic insulators. (2021) (preprint arXiv:2107.10699).
  Jianfeng Lu and Kevin D Stubbs. Algebraic localization implies exponential localization in non-periodic insulators. (2021) (preprint arXiv:2101.02626).
  Sarah Brandsen, Kevin D Stubbs, and Henry D Pfister. Reinforcement Learning with Neural Networks for Quantum Multiple Hypothesis Testing. 2020 IEEE International Symposium on Information Theory (2020) (preprint arXiv:2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching - Kevin D. Stubbs&#39;s homepage</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Courses Taught at Duke University Spring 2020, Math 112L (Calculus II) Fall 2016, Math 122L (Calculus II)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
